who are you in this scheme, it turns out, a subject, a serf, who is a
кто вы в этой схеме вы получается
slave, who do I
подданный Крепостной кто раб кто я не
know, who am I in the eyes of Putin or
знаю кто я в глазах там Путина или
Mishustin or Volodin or
мишустина или Володина или
whoever, probably, in their, in their coordinate system,
кого наверное в их в их схеме координат
I am a slave, and in your coordinate system, who are you? Listen,
я раб А в вашей системе координат кто вы
in fact, I am probably a slave
слушайте Ну по сути я наверное раб
too.
тоже Здравствуйте
Hello, I am from the Moscow region, I understand that
Здравствуйте я из Подмосковья понял вы
you are Oleg Gazmanov’s son, that you are Oleg Gazmanov’s son,
Газманова что вы сын Олега
if this is a prank, I will switch it over, it is
Газманова если это пранк я переключу это
not a
не
prank. You really look just like Oleg Gazmanov, what kind of
пранк Вы реально прямо как Олег Газманов
compliments are these, to put it mildly,
выглядите не что это за комплименты это
and what do you communicate with? Yes, in general, about anything, the court is based on your background. Well, maybe about politics. Let’s talk about politics. You are a politician. I don’t understand. What
политик ни в коем случае понял А что вас
interests you about politics? I am
интересует о
interested in the
политике Меня интересует
world. Let’s start by checking. How do we understand politics?
мир давайте для начала я хочу проверить
Who is the
Наско мы понимаем политику Кто у вас
head of the State Duma of the Russian
глава государственной Думы Российской
Federation?
Федерации слушайте у нас по-моему одна
Listen, in my opinion, we have one chapter. And
слушайте у нас по-моему одна глава И все
we all know him. Who is the head of the
мы его знаем Ну кто глава
State
государственной
Duma? In my opinion, Volodin and I
Думы блин по-моему Володин
years ago I don't know anything about me
с бы лет назад я что-то не знаю у меня у
except the word Putin honestly speaking in
меня кроме слова Путин честно говоря в
this regard And who is the head Who is the head of the
этом плане А кто глава Кто глава
government in
правительства у
your country
вас
listen I don't
слушайте Не
know shu Well listen listen We all
знаю шу Ну слушай слушайте Мы же все
understand that everyone is subordinate to one
понимаем что все подчиняются одному
person No no no you have what
человеку Нет нет нет у вас что
look you have a Constitution it
посмотрите у вас есть Конституция там же
clearly states there yes uh you have the State
чётко пишет да э у вас Государственная
Duma it is not subordinate to Putin it is a
Дума она не подчиняется Путину это
legislative body How can it be
законодательный орган Как она может
subordinate to Putin Listen I
подчиняться Путину Слушайте я вас
think I even remember you I saw you somewhere in the
по-моему даже помню я вас где-то видел в
recordings maybe yes if if I'm not
записях может быть да если если я не
mistaken you are not mistaken
ошибаюсь не ошибаетесь
probably probably not mistaken here I'm
наверное наверное не ошибаюсь вот я вам
answering you honestly as a Russian person here I
честно отвечаю как русский человек вот я
perceive all this in our country firstly it
всё это воспринимаю у нас вопервых это
changes Well as if quite often If
меняется Ну как бы довольно часто Если
you follow this
вы следите за этой
whole if I may say so party I'm
всей если можно так сказать тусовкой мне
tired of putting it there for three or
это надоело садить уже там года три или
four years already I know that there is a
четыре я вот знаю что вот есть
specific one who
конкретный
gives orders left and right in his opinion
распоряжается
That is to say you have a king you don't have a
То есть у вас царь получается у вас не у
parliament you have a king
вас нету парламента у вас царь
yes Well listen in a simplified form let's call
да Ну слушайте в упрощённом виде назовём
it
это
that way it's interesting yes I don't mind  Well, well,
так интересно да я не против нуну как бы
I wouldn't be against such a
я не против такой
Rovka Well, well, I wouldn't be against
Ровки Ну как бы не то что я не против бы
it, I understand correctly that in the
есть то я правильно понимаю что в
Russian Federation only
Российской Федерации всё решает только
one person
один человек
Putin decides everything Well, if at the highest level
Путин Ну всё если если на высшем уровне
then well, well, well, well,
то
probably listen
ну ну ну ну наверное слушайте
Come on, listen, you're talking about so many
Давай слушайте вы же Говорите настолько
different things, let's
о разных вещах давайте вы что-нибудь
ask something more complicated Well, I'm just talking
посложнее Спросите ну Я как раз вот имен
about simple names Look, I understand correctly
о простом смотрите я правильно понимаю
that you and the people of the Russian Federation Don't
что вы да народ Российской Федерации
decide anything at all, you
Ничего абсолютно не решаете у вас решает
just have one person who decides, the
просто один человек
king, this is a discovery for you Yes, I'm
царь для вас это открытие Да я вас
just asking you Yes, I
просто спрашиваю
understand, who are you in this scheme, it turns out that you are a subject Serf,
Да понял то кто вы в этой схеме вы
who is a slave,
Крепостной кто раб
who I don't know who I am in the eyes of Putin
кто я не знаю кто я в глазах там Путина
or Mishustin or Volodin or
или мишустина или Володина или
whoever, probably, in their coordinate system
кого наверное в их в их схеме координат
[music]
[музыка]
Yara And in yours,
Яра А в вашей
in the Shey sist coordinate system, who are
в Шей сист кординат кто
you now, can I have 2
вы сейчас можно 2
seconds? I just understand that I got
секунды я просто понимаю что я попадал
on the recording
на запись
[music]
[музыка]
Listen Well, in fact, I probably Well,
слы слуша Ну по сути я наверно
that is, I have some kind of
Ну то есть я с какими-то там
plans there, like, like this Can it grow into
бы планами как это Может перерасти в
another plane How is it  there you
другую плоскость Как это там куда-то
can change somewhere the main thing is that I have a
можно изменить главное чтобы там у меня
family there and all
там семья и всё
that but in their coordinate system I am
такое но в их системе координат я
absolutely exact
абсолютно точ ра
Well and I probably also want to
Ну и мне наверное как бы хочется тоже
think that I am smart but probably it is
думать что я сам умный но наверное это
not
не
so you are right you are not the most Well I don’t know I
так вы правы вы не самы Ну я не знаю я
just I just can’t
просто я просто в 2 секунды не
formulate the answer to your question in 2 seconds let
сформулирую ответ на ваш вопрос давайте
me wait formulate it in minutes well well well No well well well
я подожду сформулируйте в минуты вот ну
It will take about this
вот Нет ну не ну Это займёт по это
discussion in I’ll
обсуждение за
wait no you won’t wait this we
подожду нет вы не подождёте это у нас
will get a cut for
получится нарезка для
in an
в
hour it is Either this way or that Let’s
час это Либо так либо по-другому Давайте
talk for a long time Let’s talk for a long time
долго поговорим Давайте долго
Let’s try to talk for a long time
поговорим Давайте попробуем долго
Let’s explain to me for a long time
поговорим Давайте объясните мне долго
Then Then then let’s in more detail
Тогда Тогда Тогда давайте более детально
yes in more detail Why do you consider
да более детально Почему вы считаете
yourself a slave in Russia
себя рабом в России
yes because everything is
а да потому что всё так
built like that I’m not saying anything I don’t
построено ничего се говорю не меня не
care
дымит
thank you Well because everything is
дякую Ну потому что у нас всё так
built like that Well in the sense Well isn’t it
построено Ну в смысле Ну разве это не
clear Well why let’s say I remember there
понятно Ну а почему вот скажем Я помню
were once slave rebellions in slave countries there were
были там Восстания рабов там восстани
Spartacus’s rebellion and others Yes and why in Russia
Спартака ещё другие Да а почему в России
somehow the slaves came to terms with their  slave noun and
как-то рабы смирились свою рабской сущ
they are not conquered by anyone they
причём они не завоёваны никем они в
became slaves in their own country
своей стране стали рабами
listen I have my own answer to this
слушайте У меня есть на этот ответ свой
Lich to this question Forgive my personal
Лич на этот вопрос Простите свой личный
answer
ответ
Wow
Вай
[music]
[музыка]
and I'm just afraid that yours
а я просто боюсь что
won't like it very much Well, let's
он не очень понравится вашем Ну давайте
tell it like it is to me Yes, I don't want to
вы говорите как есть мне Да я хочу
hear a good answer And your answer is
услышать не хороший ответ А ваш ответ
real Oh, that's good, that's
настоящий О вот это хорошо вот это
good, that's what I respect, look Well,
хорошо вот это я уважаю вот смотрите
in advance Glory to Ukraine, thank you to the Heroes Glory is all
зарание Слава Украине дякую Героям Слава
at once, all at once,
это сходом вот так сходу вот
look There is a city called
смотрите Есть такой город называется
Mariupol That's where Well, for example, yes, they
Мариуполь Вот вот там Ну например да его
took it Well, to put it
вот взяли
mildly, we don't
Да ну мягко
have any complaints about it, that
говоря вот мы же ему не ваем претензии
it doesn't resist, it doesn't
что вот он не не сопротивляется он не
go to demonstrations We understand perfectly well
выходит на демонстрации Мы же прекрасно
that what will happen if a demonstration takes place in Mariupol,
что ну что произойдёт если в Мариуполе
yes, well, look, they
да да ну смотрите с Мариуполь
captured Mariupol And now they are under
их захвати Да и сейчас они вот находятся
occupation, but you, yes, in Moscow, in St. Petersburg,
в оккупации но вас же да в Москве в
in Yekaterinburg Nobody
Питере в Екатеринбурге Никто же не
captured it How did you become slaves in
захватывал Да как вы стали рабами в
your own
своей
country Sorry, just like
стране Простите точно так же как и
Mariupol people
мариупольцы
We went to
Мы выходили на
demonstrations I went to demonstrations that's
демонстрации Я выходил на демонстрации
all that happened we were all
вот всё это происходило всех нас
arrested we were all imprisoned some were
арестовывали всех нас сажали некоторых
killed some were imprisoned some like
убивали некоторых сажали некоторых вроде
me there was a so to
меня там проводили так
speak Well what is it
сказать Ну как это как это
called what is it called well like a
называется как это называется ну типа
conversation Well like a conversation like go and and not
беседы Ну типа беседы типа иди и и не
like me
вот типа меня
and
и
many of
многие
you there are a lot of people like me a lot of
ти очень много таких как я очень много
Muscovites like me a lot of
москвичей таких как я очень много
Petersburgers like me And a
питерцев таких как я И очень
lot of people like me I apologize for comparing
многие как я Я извиняюсь что Я сравниваю
but it's really like
но это действительно
that let's like well and well for a second
так давайте как бы ну и ну это секунду
it's unpleasant to admit it's painful to
это неприятно признавать это больно
admit but it's
признавать но это
like that And at what point let's say What do you
так А в какой момент вот скажем Как вы
think At what point did Russians become
считаете В какой момент русские стали
slaves in Russia Were they always like that
рабами в России Они всегда такими были
or was it in some year that happened
или там вот в какой-то год это случилось
In what year
В какой год
listen well this is already completely
слушайте ну это вообще уже прям совсем
rooted but I don't know but it's like
корнями но я не знаю но это как как
Everyone who sees who will say in How do you
Каждый кто видит кто кто скажет в Как вы
see how do you I communicate with you I'm
видите как вы я же с вами общаюсь мне
interested in how do you
интересно как вы
see how do I
видите как я
see Well I don't know listen so we
вижу Ну не знаю слушайте так мы там вам
need to blur it out with swear words no need you say
матом надо заблюрить не надо вы говорите
I then  then I won't blur it out with
я потом заблюрить
obscenities
матом
Well listen Well someone sees in this
Ну слушайте Ну кто-то видит в этом
root now I'll try
корне сейчас я попытаюсь
Priori someone sees in
Приори кто-то видит в
this 19 year someone sees in
этом 19 году кто-то видит в
this in
этом в
decay Well
распаде Ну
listen this this this this look this is a
слушай это это это это смотрите это
chain this is a chain this Well I'm interested
цепочка это цепочка это Ну мне интересно
look I'm interested specifically Not someone's
смотри мне интересно именно Не чьё-то
opinion but yours As you can see at what
мнение а ваше Как вы видите в какой
point did the Russians become slaves In ninety-
момент россияне стали рабами В девяносто
first in
первом в
1435 yesterday the day before yesterday when this this this this is a
1435 вчера позавчера когда это это это
chain this historically developed
это цепочка это исторически складывалось
over Well at least 100 years that's how
в течение Ну как минимум 100 лет
good At what point were the
вот в какой хорошо В какой момент
Russians not slaves can you name the
россияне не были рабами можете назвать
year when they were not
год когда они не были
slaves
рабами
m yes this is perhaps the most terrible question
м да это пожалуй самый страшный вопрос
these are just the
это как раз
years these are just the years of change when everything
годы это как раз годы перемен когда всё
changed when it turned out code what what
менялось когда оказалось кода что что за
years What years What years Well I don't
года Что за года Что за года Ну там не
know there deno per deno tre So you go le
знаю дено пер дено тре Так вы го ле
1917 so that is, the Russians
1917 так то есть россияне не
were not when it seemed that everything was going Well like well
было когда казалось что всё идёт Ну как
in our way That is, I understood  that
бы типа ну по нашему То есть я понял то
is, the Russians were not slaves in 1917
есть россияне не были рабами в 1917
when they made the revolution And they were not
когда сделали революцию Да и не были
slaves in
рабами в
B1 and in we are all a tree
де В1 и в мы все дерево
for a second And that is, at the time of the
на секундочку А то есть в момент
Revolution, the Russians were not slaves and
Революции россияне не были рабами а
then they became slaves again
потом снова стали
Yes, we are all like that, we all made this
Да мы все такие мы все совершили эту
mistake Well, look The point is that what
ошибку Ну смотрите Суть в том что какую
mistake and I, including, what
ошибку и я в том числе какую
mistake are you talking about I did not understand
ошибку то о чём вы говорите Не понял ещё
again what mistake we all
раз какую ошибку мы все
made, we became
совершили мы стали
slaves who are all of us I did not become a slave What are
рабами кто это все мы Я не стал рабом Да
you saying Yes, I did not become one and the Ukrainians did not become
вы что Да я не стал и украинцы не стали
slaves And that there is no war on your territory or on ours
рабами А что ни на вашей ни на нашей
And what does war
территории нет войны А причём тут война
and slavery have to do with it The war is going on because, look, it was
и рабство Война идёт потому что смотрите
not an occupier who attacked our country but we are
не оккупант напал на нашу страну но мы
not slaves, look, we have a government
не рабы у нас смотрите у нас есть власть
that we elect Yes, we decide who will be
которой мы избираем Да мы решаем кто у
our president We liked him and did
нас будет президентом понравился Он нам
not like him, we elected someone else, who will
не понравился избрали другого кто у нас
be our deputies Yes, we are not slaves, we are the
будет депутатами Да мы не рабы мы
source of power in this country Did any
источник власти в этой стране кто-нибудь
of the Ukrainians vote for you, who
из украинцев голосовал за вами кто роски
voted for Roski again, and what do you mean
голосовал за ещё раз причём смотри
Ukrainians vote
голосуют украинцы
voice Ukrainians vote for their government
голос украинцы голосуют за свою власть
slavery is the relationship between you and the government
рабство - это отношение вас и власти у
you have a Tsar to whom you are all slaves you have
вас есть Царь у которого вы все рабы вы
no influence on him in any way you cannot elect
на него не влияете никак вы не можете
him to change him he decides everything that
его избрать поменять Он решает всё что
will happen yes in Ukraine it is not like that in Ukraine there is no
будет да в Украине не так в Украине нету
Tsar in Ukraine there are citizens who
царя в Украине есть граждане которые на
elect a president at elections 4
выборах избирают президента прошло 4
years have passed yes new elections or five Yes
года да новые выборы или пять Да
they elect we did not like the previous
избирают не понравился нам предыдущий
president they elected another one there are no
президент избрали другого выбо сейчас
elections now because it is impossible to
выборов нет потому что невозможно
hold because there is a War And that's how it is yes yes that is we Well
провести потому что идёт Война А вот так
absolutely right Yes
вот да да то есть мы Ну Абсолютно верно
Now the war will end and we will hold
Да Сейчас закончится война и проведём
elections yes you and I are in
выборы да
different positions I am not a
мы с вами разном положении я же не
Perebikovsky you are reassuring
перебыковцы
yourself I am not
Я себя не
reassuring myself that so that you would not be
успокаиваю те вот для того чтобы тебе не
ashamed in front of yourself you want and
было стыдно перед собой ты хочешь а
Ukrainians are also
украинцы тоже
slaves what are you comparing with in the
рабы вы вообще с чем сравниваете в
sense I understand that I am answering a
смысле я понимаю что я отвечаю на
large audience you are telling me you are
большую аудиторию вы мне говорите ты
reassuring yourself Yes this How is it generally
себя успокаиваешь Да это Это как вообще
noticed well look you are ashamed
замечается ну так смотри тебе ээ стыдно
for yourself voicing that you are a slave in your own
для себя озвучивает что ты раб в своей
country and when you are asked that
стране и когда тебя спрашивают что
others are not slaves and  you look and you you
другие ж не рабы и ты смотри и ты ты
really in order to calm your
реально для того чтобы успокоить свою
conscience you say Well others are also
совесть ты говоришь Ну другие же тоже
slaves others in other countries are also
рабы другие в других странах тоже
slaves no guys did you have
рабы нет ребят у вас были
elections Yes there were we elected a president
выборы Да были мы избрали президента
When in the
Когда в дем
year Dem Listen well you understand what
году Слушай ну ты же понимаешь о чём
I'm asking me No I don't understand we elected a
меня спрашиваю Нет не понимаю мы избрали
president look before that we elected
президента смотри перед этим мы избрали
another president before that
другого президента перед этим ещё
another president we elect
другого президента мы избираем
presidents we elect deputies But you
президентов мы избираем депутатов А вы
don't elect you have a Tsar who
не избирает у вас есть Царь который всё
decides everything Listen listen
решает Слушай слушай
look I'm not me they don't evade at all
смотри я не я же нисколько не уклоняются
I don't argue at all with the fact that in 20
я нисколько не спорю от того что в 20
how when we re-elected
какко когда там у нас переизбрали
this well in short nothing was sorted out
этого ну короче ничего не перебирали У
You don't have
вас же нет
elections You understand what I'm talking about when
выборов Ты понял о чём я говорю когда у
we had the last elections Well you didn't have the
нас были последние выборы Ну у вас не
last elections I think in
было последние выборы по-моему в
ninety something
девяносто каком-то
everything else was an imitation of
были всё остальное это было имитация
elections
выборов у
you had listen Well you didn't even have an imitation of
вас слушайте Ну у вас даже имитации
elections you had in Dem in Dem
выборов не было у вас было в дем в дем
year you just Zelensky
году вас просто у вас просто Зеленский
said that you what in  in the nineteenth year
сказал что вы что в девятнадцатом году
we elected a president everything is fine at the
мы избрали президента всё нормально на
elections Well your president said that he
выборах Ну у вас-то президент сказал что
said that there simply won't be elections No he doesn't do
сказал что выборов просто не будет Нет
that no stop stop We
он такого не с не нет стоп стоп У нас
have a Constitution look we have a
есть Конституция смотри у нас есть
Constitution and laws Yes in which it is
Конституция и законы Да вот в которых
clearly stated Yes that during martial
Чётко сказано Да что во время военного
law elections are not held
положения выборы не проводятся
martial law will end and
закончится военное положение и
elections will be held immediately they will hold
проводятся выборы сразу они проводят
some There is a period immediately after the end of
какой-то Там срок сразу после конца
martial law so everything is clearly
военного положения так всё чётко в
spelled out in the law so the law which is the law
прописано так закон который закон
which was approved by the Ukrainian people through
который утвердил украинский народ через
their parliamentarians
своих парламентариев
Yes everything is correct And you are slaves and you want
Да всё правильно А вы рабы и ты хочешь
look you now want to prove to me a free man
смотри ты сейчас мне свободному человеку
that I am the same slave as
хочешь доказать что я такой же раб как
you no no
ты
need look we need to be
нет не надо смотри надо
free to be free People We are free
своб ыть на свободны Люде Мы свободные
people we will figure it out ourselves without you Yes
люди разберёмся сами без вас Да потому
because with us We are subjects you are an object you
что у нас Мы субъекты ты объект ты
admit yourself a
признаёшь себя
slave
рабом
Well okay let's admit this
Ну окей давай Признаем эту
formulation Super Now say this
формулировку Супер Теперь скажи такое
Why did your king decide to attack our
Почему Ваш царь решил напасть на нашу
country no wait you didn't answer me
страну нет подожди ты мне не ответил ещё
again look Let's do this I am a free man
раз смотри Давай так я свободный человек
you are a slave on this  put an end to this
ты раб на этом ставим точку в этом
issue let's move on again look No
вопросе идём дальше ещё раз смотри Нет
we're not moving on you didn't answer me I'm
мы не идём дальше ты мне не ответил во Я
asking you are you a slave are you a slave we
тебя спрашиваю ты раб ты раб мы
agreed yes I'm a free man I'm not a
согласились да Я свободный человек я не
slave I don't owe you In short wherever Hang out
раб Я не должен тебе Короче куда не
Damn please please please
Зависай Блин пожалуйста пожалуйста
such an interesting slave it's a
пожалуйста такой интересный раб
pity he hung up That's
жалко
how they all are they're all
так и они все
trying look when you
они все пытаются вот смотри когда
say you have this there and
говоришь у вас там такое а у всех стран
all the countries have the same you And all the countries are also slaves you have a
так же само вы А все страны тоже рабы у
choice everywhere there's no choice They
вас выбор в везде тоже нет выбора Они
really want to justify their slavery by the fact that
реально хотят оправдать своё рабство тем
everyone has it like that like subscribe
что так у всех вот так лайк подписка
comment and go further subscribe to my
комент и рухайся далее подпишись на мий
Instagram I don't know why you are
Instagram Я не знаю для чего це тоб Для
there Why you should watch my face
чего тоб там дивитись на оце мий фейс
But for you it's one two or three clicks
Але для тебе це один два або три клика
But you trim me and I will be KTA Wow
Але ты тримае мене и я буду КТА Вау в
I have a ton of followers and I will be in a
мене там Купа фолловер и в мене буде
great mood to make New cool
класний настрой щоб робити Нови крут
video  write to my Instagram Popik Andriy
вдео пись на мий Instagram Попик Андрий
then Come on I'll
отак Давай я тебя
wait for you and
чекаю а